Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence
    - Anna Leonowen's Gallery, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Anne, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Anne, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Anne, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Anne, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Anne and Gretchen, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Annie, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Annie, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Annie, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Annie, Ana, Barbara, Barbara L., Garrisen, Lynn, Matthew A., [1982] (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Annie and Jonathon, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Anton, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Antonacci, Lori/ Artists Talk in Art Inc., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Antupit, Samuel/Common Place Books, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Apple, Billy, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Apple, Jacki, 1986-2001 and undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - April, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Aptekarm, Ken, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Armajani, Siah, undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Armand Hammer Museum/Sexual Politics, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Arn, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Arndt, Dianne, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Arnoult, Philip, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - [Arnplausen], Carol, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Arneson, Heidi, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Art Deadlines List, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Art Dealers Association of America, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Art Hazards News, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Art Lab Inc. /Megan Pringle, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Art Matters, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Art Metropole, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Art Table, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Artists in Residence Gallery, 1983-2007 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Arts Coalition for Freedom of Expression, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Aru, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Ashley, George, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Asian Cine Vision/ Arlene Goldberg, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - [Askevold], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Askevold, David, date illegible (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Astrid, Roland, Rosemary, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Athena [Tacha], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Atkins, Robert, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Atkinson, Esther, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Atkinson, Karen, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Augustmoon, Ochiishi, 1982-2001 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Aunt Belle, undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Aunt Mary, undated (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Avocus Publishing/Jennfer Peters, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Aycock, Alice, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Aycock/ Segal, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Ayers, Robert, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - B., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - B., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - B., 2001 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - B.B., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - B.B. and Lul, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - B., Judy, undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - B.K., undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - B., Linda, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Bacon, Karin, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Baer, Josh, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Baker, Bill, undated (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Baker, Julia, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Baldely-Prschman, Sandra and Dirk, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Baldessari, Mike Fink, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Balderston, Julia (Aunt Julia), 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Baldwin, Ann and Crans, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Ball, Lillian, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Bamberg-Johnson, Matthew, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Bandman, Murray, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - The Banff Center, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Bankowsky, Jack, Charles Guarino and Knight Landesman, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Bannerman, Isabella, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Barbara, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Barbara, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Barbara, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Barbara, undated (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Barbara, undated (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Barbara and her boys, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Barbara and Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Barbiere, Patrick, Mary Taylor and Deirdre Scharffs (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Bard College/Rhea Anastas (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Bard, Perry, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Barfield, Tanya, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Barowitz, Jane and Anne Richter/ Foundation for the Community of Artists, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Barnet-Sanchez, Holly, 2007-2008, undated (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Barrett, Deirdre/CAA, 2002-2007 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Barrett/Gosin, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Barron, Susan, 1985-2001 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Barry, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Barry, undated (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Barth, Bob, undated (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Barton, Priscilla, 1988-1995 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Bartha, Catherine, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Baruch College, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Bascove, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Bastis, Kathleen, Merrry and Rad Pavelic, undated (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Batson, Bill, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Bay Area Video Coalition/ Kim Wood, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Bayer, Patricia, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Beatrice, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Beatty, Maria, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Beaumont, Betty, 1998-1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Becker, Emmanuelle and Valtors Lindbergs, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Becky, 1982-1995 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Beebe, Aaron/Coney Island Museum, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Beigle, Lauren, undated (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Beirne, Bill, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Belt, Mike, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Ben, Emily and Sarah, undated (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - Ben-Haim, Tsipi, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Benitez, Sylvia, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - Bennington College/ Elissa Tenny, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Benrabia, Sabrina, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Benson, Vickie, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Berge, Carol, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - [Berger], Ted, 1989, undated (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Berger, Theodore and Riger Bruce/New York Foundation for the Arts, 1985-2001 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Berghash, Mark, 1986-1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Berghash, Mark W. and Rachel, 1983-1998, undated (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - Berkowitz, Terry, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Berman, Jennifer/Bomb Magazine, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bernstein, Judith, 1983-2008 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Berry, Carolyn, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Berry, Michael, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Bertlmann, Renate (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Betsalel, Ken/ UNCA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Betsey, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Betty and Paul, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Beube, Douglas, 1992-2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - BEZERK productions/Linda Sibio, 2001-2005, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bill, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bill, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bill and Layne, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Bilsky, Pauline, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Blachly, Jimbo, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Blake, Nathan, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Blanka, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Blieden, Molly, 1998-2008, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Blittner, Mr. and Mrs. Adam, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Bloch, Mark, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Block, Holly/ National Association of Artists Organizations, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Block, Holly/ Art in General, 1991-1992, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Block, Holly/ Art Table, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Blog Family, 1994-2004, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Bloom, Barbara, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Bloom, Naomi Dagan, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - The Blue Noses, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Bluestone, Mimi and Herb Perr, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Blumberg, Eric, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Bob, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Bob and Olive, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Bokaer, Jonah, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Bolt, Macyn, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Bonnie, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Bonnie, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Bonnie and Ted, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Book, Lynn, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Boone, John and Jenny, 1990-1998, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Boothe, Power, 1976-2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - [Borus], Janet, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - The Boss Family, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bostric, Connie, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Bourgois, Patty, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Bowman, Robert, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Boyle, Kevin and Susan, 1976; Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Brad, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Brad, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Brad, Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Bradley, Sarah / Asian Cultural Council, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Brakely, Theresa, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Branch, Brenda Ren, 1997-2008; Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Braunstein, Jerry H., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Brazil, Pat, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Brehm, Kate, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Brendan, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Brenda, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Brill, Amy, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Britton, Susan, 1979-2000 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Brockman, Brad, 1994-2004; Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Brodsky, Judy, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Brohddus, John Eric, Undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Bronson, A.A., 2008 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Brooklyn Arts Council / Carol Sterling, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Brooklyn Friends School, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Brooklyn Historical Society / Deborah Schwartz, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Brooklyn Monthly Meeting, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Brooks, Yvonne, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Brown, Melody, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Nancy, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Brown, Robert Delford, 1976-1984 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Bruce, Rodger / Jed Berger, Undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Brunner, Helen Mary / Donald Hayes Russell, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Bruno, Joseph, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Bruns, Anne, 1998-2001; Undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Bruns, Eileen, 1998-2005 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Bruns, Eileen and Christine, 1995-2006; Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Bruns, Gustav and Anne, 1996-2000; Undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Bruns, Vince (also contains materials from Wilson), Undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Bchler, Pavel, 1989-1994; Undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Bchler, Alexandra and Pavel, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Bchler, Alexandra and Pavel, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Buckley, Brad, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Budney, Jen, 1998; Undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Building Mates, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Bunning, Emily / Treehouse Shakers, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Burdick, Karen, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Buren, Daniel, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Burgoyne, Diana, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Burkey, Wayne, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Burnham, Linda, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Burson, Nancy, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Bush Foundation / Sally Dixon, 1991-2006 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Butler, Connie, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Butler, Ken, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Buzz, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - C, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - C, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - C [Cecil] / Fordham, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Callard, Andrea; Matthew Geller, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Calvin and Patty, Undated (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Camp Onas, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Campbell, Barbara, Undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Campbell, Pamela and Wanda, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Candace, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Canley, J., Undated (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Canna, Evan, Mike, Ryann, Undated (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Carboni, Gaetano, 2006; Undated (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Carey and Michelle, Undated (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Carl and Jacquelyn, Undated (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Carla and Noel, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Carlini, John; Ben Coleman, Undated (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Carlson, Moriah, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Carmical, Lee, Undated (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Carol, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Carol, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Carol, Undated (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Carol, Undated (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Carp, Alexis Smith, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Carpenter, Mary, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Carr, Cynthia, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Carr, Robert; Theresa Tedesco, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Carrie, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Carrie, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Carsch, Ruth, 1983-1995 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Carter, Azure and Alan, 2001-2006; Undated (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Carulli, Diana, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Casa de las Americas - Gonzalo Domingo Cabrera, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Casey, Caroline, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Catalyst Arts, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Catherine, Undated (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Cembalest, Robin / ArtForum, 1983; Undated (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Center, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - The Center for Book Arts / Alexander Campos, 1994-2007 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Chalmers, Jessica, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Chamberlain, Mark; Rebecca Sherman, 1981-2006 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Chamberlain, Rebecca and Mark, 1996; Undated (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Chambers, Bruce / F.I.T., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Chambers, Bruce / F.I.T., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Champagne, Lenora, 1983-2003; Undated (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Channon, David, Undated (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Chao, Anita, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Chapman, Tim, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Char and Hannah, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Charlie, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte and Penny, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Chase, Kasem, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Chelsea Chiropractic, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Chez Bushwick, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Chinaberry Books, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Chou, Jerome / The New Press, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Chrissie, Illegible (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Christa and [Jill], 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Christian, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - [Christon], Alice, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Chris, Cynthia / Printed Matter, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Christov, Alice; George Moore / Intercambios Culturales of El Salvador, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Christov; Moore, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Chunn, Nancy, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Cindy, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Circle of Gold, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Claire, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Claire, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Clarke, John P., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Clarke, Elly, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Claus and Ariane, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Clinton, Bill (Democratic National Convention), Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Cloud, Lea, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Clough, Charles, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - CNN / Gail Evans, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Coates, Brenda, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Cockburn Family, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Cockburn, Stormie [and girls], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Coco, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Cody, Steven / Ski Windam, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Coggeshall, Agnes W., 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Cognita, N. Vernita, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Cohen, Charles / University of Chicago, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Cohen, Elaine Lustig, Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Cohen, Norma, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Cohen, Ruth, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Coleman, Anna, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Coleman, Grisha, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Coleman, Mimsie, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Colleen, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Colleen and Chris, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - College Art Association / Mary-Beth Shine, 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Colmer, Roy, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Colo, Papo and Jeanette Ingberman, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Colombatto, Perhi, 1991, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Comfort Family, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Connor, Maureen, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Contento/O'Malley, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Con Edison, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Contemporary Art Institute of Detroit, undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Conwill, Kinshasha, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Cook, Richard and Doris, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Cook, Scott, 1988-2005 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Cook, Scott, 1985-1986, undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Cook, Susana, 2001-2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Cook-Wilson, Comley, 1997-2003, undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Cooper-Henry, Adjowii, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Copp, Fletcher, 1996, undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - [Corin] Nina, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Corlin, Kelli, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Coro Foundation/ Andrew Rubinson, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence from Martha, no address, undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence neither to nor from Wilson, 1986, 1991, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Cortigan, Steven, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Constanzo, Jim/RePo History, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Constantino, Roselyn, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Costello, Terence, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Cottingham, Laura, 1994-2007 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Coulson, Anthony J., 1992 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Covan, Ellie/Dixon Place, 1991-2006, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Ellie [Covan] and [Lauren], undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Cowboy John, Spider Webb, Phil Jonns, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Coyne, Petah, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Cramer, Erin, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Crandall, Jordan/ X-Art Foundation, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Crane, Mike (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Crash, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Crawford, Cair, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Crawford, Frank, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Creative Time, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Crest, William, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Croll-Smith, Caroline, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cronin, Ciara/ James O'Malley P.C., 2005 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Cronin, Kelly/ Wayne State, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Cross Section Exhibition/ Marcella Steingart, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Crotty, James, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Crowly, Mary, undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Crowne, Melchia, 1987-1991, undated (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Culkin, Jody, 1988-1997, undated (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Cullen, Kathleen and Denis Ray, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Cullen, Deborah, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - R. Cumming, undated (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Cummings, Linda, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Cunningham, Elena, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Curmano, Billy, 1994-2000 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Cushmore, Edna and Larry, 1967-2001, undated (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Cutforth, Roger, undated (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Cypis, Dorit, 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Cypis. Dorit with enclosure (wrapped in paper), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - D, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - D (vg), undated (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - D [Dlier], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - D, L, O, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - D + M, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - D'Amato, Alfonse, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - D'arc, Victor and Mary Lee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - DaDao Live Art Festival/ Shu Yang, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Dalby, Marcia, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - dal Doggetto, Lynne, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Dallas-Swann, Susan/Ohio State University, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Dan, undated (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Dan, undated (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Dan, date illegible, undated (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Dana, undated (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Danforth, Isabelle (Aunt Belle), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Danilova, Ivina, 1997-2008, undated (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Dannasch, Ariane, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Danneels, Veronique/Trouble Performance Festival, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Danny, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Dantzier, Kurt, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Darley Skip, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Darlington, Doug, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Dave and Diana, undated (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Dave, undated (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - David, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - David, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - David, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - David, undated (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - David and Elaine, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - David and Judy, undated (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Davies, Cristyn, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Davis, Douglas, 1976-1997 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Davis, Douglas and Jane Bell, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Davis, Paula/Lolita Productions includes SAG contract, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Davis, Scott, 1978-2004, undated (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Davis, Zebra, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Deagan, Mary Ellen/ Office of Children and Family Services, undated (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - deBeer, Sue, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - deCamp, Kyle, 1998-2005 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - DeSando, Sandra, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Dean, David/ Printed Matter, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Deb, undated (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Deb, ca. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Deborah, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Deborah, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Deborah, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Deborah, undated (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - Del Re, Alexander, 1998-2007 (Box 9, Folder 149)
    - DeMonte, Claudia and Ed McDawin, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 150)
    - Demorizzi Silvio, NEA, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - Dena, undated (Box 9, Folder 152)
    - Denes, Agnes, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 153)
    - Denise, 1977-1985, undated (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Dennis, Charles, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Depas, Albert/ Mega Press, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - dePorter, Janna, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - DePorter, Kathleen, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Deporter, Patti, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - DeSalvo, Donna, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Des Becker, Claire, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - Deumens, Johan, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Dewey, Ariane, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Deutsch, Jeffery, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Develop Don't Destroy Brooklyn, 2005-2006, undated (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - Devine, Maya and Stuart Steinfeld, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - DeVita, Julia, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - DeWys, Margaret, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Diamond, Dennis, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Diane, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Diane, Marcel and Martina, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Diaz, Ryder, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Dibell, Dominique, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 173)
    - Dickson, Emma, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 174)
    - Diggs, Peggy, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Dion, Judith, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Diner, Chris, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Di Palma, Ray, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Dixon. Jenny, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Diverse Forms for New York State, 1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Do It Yourself Art Exhibit/Anne Dorothee Bohme/ Kevin Henry/ Lindsay Bosch, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Dobrian, Christopher, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Doctorow. Erica, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Dodge, Patricia/ The Macdowell Colony Inc., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Dodge, Robert, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Doherty, Delia, [1981] (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Dominic, Magie, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Donahue, Neil, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Donini, Marilynn/Philip Morris Companies, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Donna, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 15)